andalucia.com 2019-06-09

# Andalucia.com - Privacy Policy

By means of this notification, **Andalucia.com SLu,** domiciled at **Avd. del Carmen 9 Edf. Puertosol, 1ª planta Oficina 30, Estepona, telephone:** **+34 952 897 865** email: **info@andaluciaws.com** (hereinafter, the COMPANY) hereby informs its users **in compliance with article 5 of Organic Law 15/1999** , of 13 December, 1999, on personal data protection (hereinafter LOPD) of its personal data protection policy, in order that they may expressly, freely and voluntarily decide to provide **Andalucia.com SLu** with the personal data requested of them by the website for the provision of its services.

Users are also hereby informed that the data collected is incorporated in a file that is duly registered with the General Data Protection Register, the owner and responsible party of which is **Andalucia.com SLu** , who keeps a mixed file of data in accordance with the specified aims and other provisions established in this privacy policy, for which you grant us your express and unequivocal consent.

Collection of data and planned usage.

Personal data is collected through the filling in of possible methods of sending data: either through a contact form (or other available forms) that appears on the web page, or the sending of email. Only adequate, pertinent and non-excessive amounts of data are requested in relation to the determined, explicit and legitimate area, purposes and services of **Andalucia.com SLu**. The user must fill in the forms with true, exact, complete and up-to-date data, and shall be liable for any damages or injury that may occur as a result of filling in the form incorrectly with data that is false, inexact, incomplete or not up-to-date.

A. Companies and personal data

Data on companies and, in particular, on people that is received through information request forms, or other demands made to the person responsible for the file, shall be processed for the purpose of dealing with the request, as well as to provide information that may be of interest about our current and future products and services.

**By clicking the “SEND” button that appears on the information request form (CONTACT - OR OTHER DATA SENDING OPTIONS), it shall be understood as expressly accepted that the data will be processed for the aforementioned purposes,** in accordance with the requirements set forth in article 21 of Law 34/2002, on Information Society and Electronic Commerce Services, for sending commercial communications by email and other equivalent means.

Users may oppose their data being processed for the aforementioned purposes by sending a letter by post to the address Avd. del Carmen 9 Edf. Puertosol 1ª planta Oficna 30, Estepona, through the procedure that authorises **Andalucia.com SLu** in each case, and by providing proof of identity in order to exercise this right to opposition.

Use of Cookies

We may use outside companies to display ads and collect information on our site. These ads may contain cookies for optimization purposes, and we do not have access to this information. These companies may use this information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on site, other Web sites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information. For more information, or to learn about opting-out of such advertising technologies, please visit: **<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> **and **www.google.com**

Security Measures

**Andalucia.com SLu** has adopted the personal data protection security levels required by current data protection legislation, and has installed the technical and organisational measures necessary to prevent loss, incorrect use, alteration, unauthorised access and other possible risks. Similarly, **Andalucia.com SLu** is obligated to comply with the obligation to keep the data contained in the computerised file confidential, as established in the applicable data protection legislation.

Particularly, **Andalucia.com SLu** hereby states that it has signed any pertinent data confidentiality and protection agreements with third parties that have access to the personal data under the responsibility of **Andalucia.com SLu** in order to provide service to this party, in compliance with the provisions of article 12 of the LOPD; these third parties undertake to process the data for the sole purpose of providing the services contracted by **Andalucia.com SLu** and to adopt any computational, organisational and any other type of security measures that may be required in each case. **Andalucia.com SLu** hereby states that the website collects data in a technological environment that applies high levels of security and confidentiality when transmitting the information. This notwithstanding, the User should be aware that Internet security measures are not impregnable.

Exercising rights to access, rectification, cancellation and opposition.

Users or their proxies may at any time exercise their right to access, rectification, cancellation and, if applicable, opposition in accordance with that set forth in the LOPD and other legislation applicable to this effect; these rights may be exercised by sending notification in writing to **Andalucia.com SLu** , domiciled at Avd.del Carmen 9 Edf.puerto Sol 1ªplanta Of.30, Estepona in which proof of the user's identity should be provided, or to the e-mail address info@andaluciaws.com.

**Andalucia.com SLu** reserves the right to modify this data privacy policy to adapt it to new legislation or jurisprudence, as well as to any interpretations of this legislation that may be published by the Spanish Data Protection Agency. In this case, **Andalucia.com SLu** shall announce said changes on the website a sufficient amount of time prior to their implementation.

Back to top
